https://thekiteshoppe.com/privacy/

Loading... Please wait...
Products
Sport/Stunt KitesQuad Line KitesIndoor KitesParts & Supplies
Privacy
What information do we collect?To complete an online purchase on www.TheKiteShoppe.com, you will need to create an account. Your account is protected by a password that you choose. We will ask for your name, email address, billing and shipping addresses and telephone numbers. This account information is kept along with your order history. You can view your account information and the status of your orders by clicking on the "YOUR ACCOUNT" page at any time. We do not store credit card information on the server.In addition, we also log information about your visit to the store, including the URL that you came from, your Internet Protocol address, domain type (e.g., .com, .org), and The Kite Shoppe pages that you view and search terms you use, none of which is assigned to your account, all information is collected generically for monthly product popularity and visitor statistics.
How do we protect your information via the web?
When using The Kite Shoppe shopping cart, your credit card and personal details are protected by PostiveSSL® - 128 bit SSL encryption, which you can see engage during the check out process using our shopping cart (httpS://).
The SSL (and TLS) protocol is the Web standard for encrypting communications between users and SSL (secure sockets layer) e-commerce sites. Data sent via an SSL connection is protected by encryption, a mechanism that prevents eavesdropping and tampering with any transmitted data. SSL provides businesses and consumers with the confidence that private data sent to a Web site, such as credit card numbers, are kept confidential. Web server certificates (also known as secure server certificates or SSL certificates) are required to initialize an SSL session.Customers know when they have an SSL session with a website when their browser displays the little gold padlock and the address bar begins with a https rather than http. SSL certificates can be used on webservers for Internet security and mailservers such as imap, pop3 and smtp for mail collection/sending security.
How do we use personal information?The information you provide to purchase merchandise from The Kite Shoppe web site is used to fulfill your order. In addition, you may choose to receive an email newsletter with special promotions, new arrivals or new features of the site. You can remove yourself from our newsletter list by changing your selection on the "YOUR ACCOUNT" page at any time.In addition, we use log information from The Kite Shoppe web site in order to enhance the operation of the Store. We do not correlate personally identifying information collected on The Kite Shoppe web site with any other information that you provide when using other The Kite Shoppe products or services (i.e. discussion forum).What about cookies?A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. When you visit The Kite Shoppe web site, we set a cookie on your computer to help identify you, customize your experience and maintain your account and order information. To protect the security of your account, you must accept The Kite Shoppe web site cookie in order to shop here.Do we share personal information?The Kite Shoppe is operated by our staff to fulfill your orders. As such, The Kite Shoppe may collect and share your information to fulfill your order. We do not sell or rent any personal information to others. We may, however, disclose personal information if we believe we are required to do so by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of The Kite Shoppe, its users and the public.Personal information collected by The Kite Shoppe may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which The Kite Shoppe or its agents maintain facilities. By using The Kite Shoppe web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.How do I update my information?You can access and edit your account information at any time by logging in and clicking on the "YOUR ACCOUNT" link, found near the upper right corner of any page. If you have questions about the status of your orders or any other questions about the The Kite Shoppe, please contact us.Changes to this PolicyPlease note that it is possible that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page so that you can easily find the information we collect and how we safeguard it.
Brands
Goodwinds Laser Pro Prism Premier Kites The Kite Shoppe Sky Shark 3Wind R Sky Challenge HQ Kites
After a couple months of rehearsals, Epcot Forever debuted on October 1st, 2019 …
WSKIF videos past and present!
WSIKF August 2019 - Stack Fly!!video by Nic O'Neill of Fortuna FoundWSIKF …
NBC Brian Williams Rock Center
I'm just so proud of the iQuad team! They have been getting a lot of press …
Sport/Stunt KitesQuad Line KitesIndoor KitesParts & Supplies
All prices are in USD. © 2020 The Kite Shoppe.
Sitemap |
Shopping Cart Software by BigCommerce
